

ASHLEE S. CLEVELAND

Interior Stylist + Product & Graphic Designer

Summary

Highly creative and multitalented Designer with extensive experience in fashion, Interiors, product design, graphics & marketing. Exceptional collaborative and interpersonal skills; dynamic team player with well-developed written and verbal

Service

US Army Reserves

- 2002 2018
- COMSEC
- Radio Repail
- Convoy Logistics
- Access Guard
- OIF: Iraq 2005 2006
- OEF: Iraq 2007 2008

Skilis

- Space Planning
- Organization
- Color Theory
- Sourcine
- Merchandising
- Social Media
 Management
- Content Creation

EMPLOYMENT

Visual Merchandiser

2019 - Present

At Home Decor Superstore

- Styles + stocks welcome, feature and main table displays to demonstrate current trends and highlight promotional sales.
- Styles + stocks quarterly design vignettes to display new merchandise and drive sales
- Performs store conditioning tasks and housekeeping (inside and out) tasks as assigned.
- Maintains 5S standards (Sort, Straighten, Systematic cleanup, Standardize and Sustain) in all areas excluding receiving.
- Operates all equipment in a safe manner per directed procedures.
- Amplified conversational and negotiating acumen and verbal skills.

Interior Stylist, Product Designer

2017: Present

Ashlee Dominic Design, LLC

- Determines the look and feel of clients' homes by selecting and placing decorative elements such as paint, textiles, and furniture.
- Makes interior spaces functional and safe by determining space requirements.
- Composing mood boards +3D rendering of client spaces.
- Sourcing products and materials
- Managing labor and installation processes
- Conceptualizing new product ideas
- Creating prototypes to be used in pitch proposals and product demonstrations.



ASHLEE S. CLEVELAND

Interior Stylist + Product & Graphic Designer

EDUCATION

B.F.A AIU Atlanta, GA 2010 - 2012 Fashion Marketing Fashion Design GPA: 3.86

Boxercraft, Inc. 2011 Marketing Internship

Technology

Microsoft Office

Adobe Suite

IBM AS 400

Scan / Copy / Fax

Typing / 10 - key

CONTACT

Phone **678** 354 1244

EMAIL ashleedominicdesign@gmail.com

EMPLOYMENT

Product Designer
Halo Slippers
2017 - 2019

Valentina Lucci, LLC

- Co-designed paten-pending Halo Slipper
- Created Initial prototypes of functioning Halo Slippers
- Patternmaking + grafting slipper patterns
- Construction of presentation Halo Slipper prototypes.
- Small production run manufacturing.
- Pitching to online + brick and mortar retailers

Style Consultant Michael Kors Account 2014 Seasonal

Donnelley Communications

- Captured and analyzed user feedback and responded to written communications.
- Improved customer service quality results by evaluating and updating processes.
- Maintained a high level of quality assurance by proofreading.
- Handled customer inquiries with the highest degree of courtesy and professionalism.

HOBBIES + INTERESTS









Interiors

Fashion

Craft Art Graphic Design